<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
  <apps>
  </apps>
  <app id="etflix">
    <name>Netflix</name>
    <version>6.99.5.0</version>
    <icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/Logo.Store.scale-100-1776508469.png</icon>
    <publisher>Netflix, Inc.</publisher>
    <featured>false</featured>
    <description>Looking for the most talked about TV shows and movies from around the world? They’re all on Netflix.&#13;
&#13;
We’ve got award-winning series, movies, documentaries, and stand-up specials. And with the mobile app, you get Netflix while you travel, commute, or just take a break.&#13;
&#13;
What you’ll love about Netflix:&#13;
- We add TV shows and movies all the time. Browse new titles or search for your favorites, and stream videos right on your device.&#13;
- The more you watch, the better Netflix gets at recommending TV shows and movies you’ll love.&#13;
- Enjoy a safe watching experience just for kids with family-friendly entertainment.&#13;
- Preview quick videos of our series and movies and get notifications for new episodes and releases.&#13;
&#13;
Netflix membership is a month-to-month paid subscription that begins at sign up. You can easily cancel anytime, online, 24 hours a day. There are no long-term contracts or cancellation fees. We just want you to love what you watch.&#13;
&#13;
By clicking INSTALL, you consent to the installation of the Netflix application and any updates or upgrades thereto.</description>
    <package>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/4DF9E0F8.Netflix_6.99.5.0_neutral_-_mcm4njqhnhss8-1776508466.appxbundle</package>
    <screenshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/netflix_scr1-1776508470.png</screenshot1>
    <screenshot2>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/netflix_scr2-1776508472.png</screenshot2>
    <screenshot3>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/netflix_scr3-1776508474.png</screenshot3>
    <pcCapable>true</pcCapable>
    <mobileCapable>true</mobileCapable>
  </app>
</data>
